Guide to the New York Building Congress Records WAG.167
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series III: General Files, 1918-2011
  - Building Code, New York City: Industry Advisory Committee, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Building Code, New York City: Industry Advisory Committee, 1965-1967 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Building Code, New York City: Public Hearing Statements, 1967-1968 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Building Code, New York City: Publicity, 1959-1960 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Building Code, New York City: Publicity, 1961 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Building Code, New York City: Publicity, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Building Code, New York City: Publicity, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - Building Code, New York City: Publicity, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Building Code, New York City: Publicity, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - Building Code, New York City: Publicity, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - Building Code, New York City: Publicity, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - Building Code, New York City: Publicity, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 46)
  - Building Code, New York City: Publicity, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 47)
  - Building Code, New York City: Revisions, 1969-1973 (Box 10, Folder 48)
  - Building Industry Employers Association Convention, Dec 1952 (Box 10, Folder 49)
  - Building Industry Employers Association: Legislative Committee, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 50)
  - Building Industry Employers Association: Legislative Committee, 1980-1981 (Box 10, Folder 51)
  - Building Industry Employers Association: Legislative Committee, 1982-1983 (Box 10, Folder 52)
  - Building the City of the 21st Century (New York City Government), 1993 (Box 10, Folder 53)
  - Building Trade Employers Association, 1949, Undated (Box 10, Folder 54)
  - Building Trade Employers Association: News and Opinion, 1949 (Box 10, Folder 55)
  - Building Trade Employers Association: News and Opinion, 1953 (Box 10, Folder 56)
  - Building Trade Employers Association: News and Opinion, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 57)
  - Building Owners' and Managers' Association of Greater New York: Newsletter, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 58)
  - Burns, Jeremiah, 1960-1967 (Box 10, Folder 59)
  - Business Committee on Midtown Traffic, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 60)
  - Business Council of New York State, inc., 1988-1989 (Box 10, Folder 61)
  - Business for Efficient Transportation: Press Release, Undated (Box 10, Folder 62)
  - Business Marketing Corporation for New York City (Pamphlet), circa 1978 (Box 10, Folder 63)
  - Business Roundtable: Subjects of Bargaining, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 64)
  - Center for Construction Industry Studies, Proposal, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 65)
  - Chamber of Commerce of the United States: Congressional Action, 1978-1980 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Citizens Housing and Planning Council: The Assessor, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Clippings, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Clippings, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Clippings, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Clippings, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Clippings, 1980-1982 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Clippings, 1982-1985 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Clippings, 1986-1988 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Clippings, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Clippings, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Clippings, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Clippings, Undated (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Coalition for Equitable Construction Contracts, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Code of Ethics for the Building Industry: Exposition, Undated (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Columbia University: Manhattanville Expansion, Undated (Box 11, Folder 16a)
  - Commercial Rent Control, 1986-1988 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Committee for Casino Gaming of New York City: "Case for Casino Gambling", 1981 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Community Planning Districts: History, Map, etc., 1968 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Comptroller Functions in New York City and in Other Jurisdictions: Report by H.D. Underhill, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Con Edison (Pamphlet), 1981 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Connecticut Building Congress (Pamphlet), 1960 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Consolidated Carting Corporation, 1958 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Construction Coordinator, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Construction Cost Pamphlet, 1956 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Construction Cost Task Force, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Construction Cost Trend Report, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Construction Finance Manager's Association: "New York Construction Market in the 1990s", 1988 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Construction Industry Publicity Program Report [additional copy in oversize box 23], circa 1947 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Contract Settlements: Memo Draft, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Contractors: Eligibility Regulations, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Contractors: Performance Evaluations, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Corporate Codes of Conduct, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Correspondence, 1930 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Correspondence, 1954 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Correspondence, 1958 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Correspondence, 1969-1970 (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Correspondence, 1972-1974 (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Correspondence, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Correspondence, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - Correspondence, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - Correspondence, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - Correspondence, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - Correspondence, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 45)
  - Correspondence, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 46)
  - Correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box 11, Folder 47)
  - Correspondence, Jan-Jun 1986 (Box 11, Folder 48)
  - Correspondence, Jul-Dec 1986 (Box 11, Folder 49)
  - Correspondence, Jan-Mar 1987 (Box 11, Folder 50)
  - Correspondence, Apr-Aug 1987 (Box 11, Folder 51)
  - Correspondence, Sep-Dec 1987 (Box 11, Folder 52)
  - Correspondence, Jan-Jun 1988 (Box 11, Folder 53)
  - Correspondence, Jul-Dec 1988 (Box 11, Folder 54)
  - Correspondence, Jan-Jun 1989 (Box 11, Folder 55)
  - Correspondence, Jul-Sep 1989 (Box 11, Folder 56)
  - Correspondence, Oct-Dec 1989 (Box 11, Folder 57)
  - Correspondence, Jan-Jun 1990 (Box 11, Folder 58)
  - Correspondence, Jul-Dec 1990 (Box 11, Folder 59)
  - Correspondence, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 60)
  - Correspondence, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 61)
  - Correspondence, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 62)
  - Correspondence, Jan-Feb 1995 (Box 11, Folder 63)
  - Correspondence, Mar-Jun 1995 (Box 11, Folder 64)
  - Correspondence, Jul-Sep 1995 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, Oct-Dec 1995 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, Jan-Mar 1996 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, Apr-Jun 1996 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, Jul-Dec 1996 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 2005-2007 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, Undated (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence: Position Letters, 2002-2007 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence: Position Letters, 2008-2009 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Courter, Joseph, Various (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Crane Regulations, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - "Decision '89" (NYBC), 1989 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Discrimination in New York City Construction Trades (Report, New York City Commission on Human Rights), 1993 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Edifice, 1960-1965 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Edifice, 1970-1977 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Edifice, 1980-1982 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Electrical Code, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Electricity Outlook, 2001, 2006 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Eller, Peter W. "Teamwork in Building" ( Elks Magazine), 1948 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Ellis Island Medal of Honor, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - (e)Update, 2003-2007 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Exploring Economic Development Opportunities in Recycling, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Fair Labor Standards Act As Amended (Bureau of National Affairs), 1949 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Federal City Council: Annual Report, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Federal Home Loan Bank of Seattle (Pamphlet), 1979 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Federal Trade Commission, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Fenner Memorial Fund, 1927 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Forum Club, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Fouilhoux, J. Andre (President, NYBC): Death Announcement and Tribute, 1945 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Grand Central Station Renovation, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Gun Hill Road Retail Development, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Harbour Village Housing Project, 1970-1972 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - "History of the Inception of the Congress Movement" (Kohn), circa 1924 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Holden, Thomas: Address to the Chicago Building Congress, 1938 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Home Improvement, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Housing Maintenance Code, 1967-1969 (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Hudson River Project: Water Tunnel #3, 1977-1980 (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Hult, Eugene E.: Fellowship Fund, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - ICONN Project: New York Waterway and Port Modernization, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - "Impact of Insurance Issues on New York City's Construction Industry", 2004 (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - Index of Construction Contract Value (1921-1970), 1971 (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - Industry Promotion Fund, 1992-1993 (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - Institute of Public Administration: Contracting in New York City Government, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 44)
  - Institute for Transportation Systems, City University of New York: Private Sector in Public Transportation in New York City (Draft), 1990 (Box 12, Folder 45)
  - "Jobs and Economic Regeneration in New York City (Business/Labor Working Group), circa 1976 (Box 12, Folder 46)
  - Jordan, Vernon, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 47)
  - Legislation: Battery Park City Authority, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 48)
  - Legislation: City Housing Authority Law, 1957-1958 (Box 12, Folder 49)
  - Legislation: Community Development Amendment, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 50)
  - Legislation: Construction Superintendents, 1960-1969 (Box 12, Folder 51)
  - Legislation: Construction Waste Fees, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 52)
  - Legislation: Correspondence, 1974, 1982-1983 (Box 12, Folder 53)
  - Legislation: Department of Buildings Fee Increases, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 54)
  - Legislation: Department of Buildings (New), 1972 (Box 12, Folder 55)
  - Legislation: Energy Conservation Bill, 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 56)
  - Legislation: Engineering, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 57)
  - Legislation: Environmental Quality Bond Act, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 58)
  - Legislation: Height of Buildings, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 59)
  - Legislation: High Rise Law, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 60)
  - Legislation: Internal Revenue Service Proposals (Long-Term Contracts), 1972 (Box 12, Folder 61)
  - Legislation: Kalisch-Jarcho Bill, 1983-1984 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Legislation: Labor Reform Act, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Legislation: Lobbying Bill, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Legislation: Noise Code, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Legislation: Noise Control Code, 1971-1973 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Legislation: Wicks Law, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Letters to the Editor, 1984-1989 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Letters to the Editor, 1990-1996 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Letters to the Editor, 2000-2006 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Letters to the Editor, Undated (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Lindsay, John V., 1967 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Literature Requests: "Recommendations on 'or Equal Clause'", Jun 1963 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Literature Requests: "Recommendations on 'or Equal Clause'", Jul 1963-Mar 1964 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Lower Manhattan Expressway, 1963-1965 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Lower Manhattan Expressway, 1966-1969 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Mall at Rego Park, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - "Mandate Millstone" (Mayor Koch Statement at U.S. Conference of Mayors), Jan 1980 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - "Market Letter: A Digest of Construction Markets & Trends", 1962-1963 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Mayoral Committees, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Mayor's Task Force on Reorganization of New York City Government, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Mayor's Task Force on Reorganization of New York City Government, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Measurement of the Size and Importance of the Construction Industry in the Economy of New York City, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Measurement of the Size and Importance of the Construction Industry in the Economy of New York City, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Measurement of the Size and Importance of the Construction Industry in the Economy of New York City: Correspondence, 1966-1967 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Metrobuild, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Metrobuild, 1988-1989 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Minority Gains in New York Construction Jobs (Pamphlet), 1979 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - MIUS Forum, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Moses, Robert, 1965-1978 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Municipal Services Administration, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - National Asbestos Council, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - National Association of Women in Construction, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - National Building Museum Award Dinner, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - National Bureau of Standards, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - National Congress of the Building and Construction Industry, 1929-1936 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - National Construction Employers Council, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - National Federation of Building Industries, 1918 (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - National Institute of Building Sciences, 1982, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - New Buildings: Cost, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - New Jersey Advisory Council on Vocational Education, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - New York Alliance for the Public Schools, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - New York Association of Consulting Engineers, 1982-1991 (Box 13, Folder 42)
  - NYBC History, 1924-1984, Undated (Box 13, Folder 43)
  - NYBC News, 1933-1945 (Box 13, Folder 44)
  - NYBC News, 1950-1951 (Box 13, Folder 45)
  - NYBC News, 1955 (Box 13, Folder 46)
  - "New York Building Trades," Chapter 4 of Trade Unionism and Labor Problems, John R. Commons, Undated (Box 13, Folder 47)
  - New York Carpenters Labor-Management: Reception for A. D'Amato, Feb 17, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 48)
  - New York Chamber of Commerce, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 49)
  - New York Chamber of Commerce: Great New York City Turnaround Begins, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 50)
  - New York Chamber of Commerce: History, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 50a)
  - New York City Board of Standards and Appeals, 1957 (Box 13, Folder 51)
  - New York City Board of Standards and Appeals, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 52)
  - New York City Building Code Commission, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 53)
  - New York City Bureau of Labor Services, 1980-1981 (Box 13, Folder 54)
  - New York City: Capital Commitments, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 55)
  - New York City Capital Projects, 1979-1989 (Box 13, Folder 56)
  - New York City Charter Revision: Alliance for a Better Charter, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - New York City Charter Revision: Charter Provisions on Contracting and Procurement, Undated (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - New York City Charter Revision: Charter Provisions on Property Management, Undated (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - New York City Charter Revision: Charter Provisions on Public Construction, Undated (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - New York City Charter Revision: The Charter Review, 1987-1989 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - New York City Charter Revision: Clippings, 1987-1989 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - New York City Charter Revision: Contracting and Procurement for City Goods, Services and Construction, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - New York City Charter Revision: Correspondence, 1987-1989 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - New York City Charter Revision: Land Governance and the New York City Charter, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - New York City Charter Revision: Land Governance and the New York City Charter (Volume 2), 1988 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - New York City Charter Revision: Neighborhoods, Land Use and the New York City Charter, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - New York City Charter Revision: NYBC Proposals and Statements, 1987-1989 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - New York City Charter Revision: New York City Charter, 1985-1987 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - New York City Charter Revision: New York City Charter Revision Commission, 1987-1989 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - New York City Charter Revision: New York City Charter Revision Commission, Chair's Recommendations, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - New York City Charter Revision: New York City Charter Revision Commission, Initial Proposals, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - New York City Charter Revision: New York City Charter Revision Commission, Meeting Notices, 1988-1989 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - New York City Charter Revision: New York City Charter Revision Commission, Preliminary Proposals, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - New York City Charter Revision: New York City Charter Revision Commission, Press Releases, 1988-1989 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - New York City Charter Revision: New York City Charter Revision Commission, Proposal Summaries, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - New York City Charter Revision: New York City Charter Revision Commission, Proposal Summaries, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - New York City Charter Revision: New York City Charter Revision Commission, Proposals, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - New York City Charter Revision: New York City Charter Revision Commission, Publications, 1988-1989 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - New York City Charter Revision: Proposals and Statements, 1988-1989 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - New York City Charter Revision: Proposed Charter, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - New York City Charter Revision: State Charter Revision Commission for New York City, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - New York City Charter Revision: Testimony, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - New York City Civil Defense: Emergency Equipment Survey, 1958 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - New York City Commissioner of Buildings: Candidates, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - New York City Comptroller, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - New York City Construction Outlook (NYBC), 2000-2007 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - New York City Construction Outlook (NYBC), 2008-2009 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - New York City Council: Codification Committee, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - New York City Department of Buildings, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 33a)
  - New York City Department of Buildings Reorganization: Mayor John V. Lindsey Correspondence, 1966 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - New York City Department of Buildings Reorganization: Meetings, 1966 (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - New York City Department of Design and Construction (proposed): Task Force, 1995-1996 (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - New York City Department of General Services: Upcoming Projects, 1993-1994 (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - New York City Department of Housing Preservation and Development: Correspondence, 1979-1982 (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - New York City Department of Transportation: Bridge Programs, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - New York City Department of Transportation: Report, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 40)
  - New York City Departments Reorganization (Mayor Lindsay's Plan), 1966-1967 (Box 14, Folder 41)
  - New York City Economic Policy and Marketing Group: Job Creation Strategies, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 42)
  - New York City: Executive Budget, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 43)
  - New York City Housing and Development Administration, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - New York City Housing Partnership, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - New York City Housing Partnership: Land Development Guide, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - New York City Office of Director of Construction, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - New York City Office of Management and Budget, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - New York City Public Development Corporation: Financial Planning and Analysis Scope of Services, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - New York City: Rezoning, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - New York City School Construction Authority, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - New York City School Construction Authority, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - New York City Service Crisis: A Management Response, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - New York City Transit Authority, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - New York City Transportation Administration: Manhattan Truck Route Study, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - New York Construction, Jan 2011 (Box 15, Folder 12a)
  - New York Construction News, 1955 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - New York Construction News, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - New York Construction News, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - New York Construction Users Council, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - New York Construction Users Council, Undated (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - New York Interagency Engineering Committee, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - New York Society of Association Executives, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - New York Society of Association Executives: Government Affairs Committee, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - New York Society of Association Executives: Government Affairs Committee, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - New York Society of Association Executives: Government Affairs Committee, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - New York Society of Association Executives: Government Affairs Committee, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - New York State Advisory Commission to the U.S. Commission on Civil Rights: "Discrimination in the Building Trades", 1963 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - New York State Organized Crime Task Force: Corruption and Racketeering in the New York City Construction Industry, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - New York State Power Authority: Report on Hydroelectric Power, circa 1980 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - New York State Society of Professional Engineers, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - New York State Society of Professional Engineers, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - New York State Temporary Commission on Lobbying, 1988-1989 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - New York World's Fair (1964-1965), 1961 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - News and Issues (NYBC Newsletter), 2003-2006 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - NYC2012 (Olympic Bid), 2002-2004 (Box 15, Folder 31a)
  - Perkins Eastman Architects: 10th Anniversary Pamphlet, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Port Authority Agenda Letter, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - Port Authority of New York and New Jersey: Truck Commodity Survey, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - Pratt Institute: New York City Building Laws Seminar, Undated (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - Press Coverage of NYBC, 1986-1987 (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - Press Coverage of NYBC, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - Press Coverage of NYBC, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 38)
  - Press Coverage of NYBC, 1995-1999 (Box 15, Folder 39)
  - Press Coverage of NYBC, 2005-2008 (Box 15, Folder 40)
  - Press Coverage of NYBC, Undated (Box 15, Folder 41)
  - Press Releases, 1946, 1952 (Box 15, Folder 42)
  - Press Releases, 1986-1988 (Box 15, Folder 43)
  - Press Releases, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 44)
  - Press Releases, 1995-1996 (Box 15, Folder 45)
  - Press Releases, 2000-2007 (Box 15, Folder 46)
  - Press Releases, Undated (Box 15, Folder 47)
  - Pride: St. Louis Construction Industry Labor-Management Coalition, 1975-1977 (Box 15, Folder 48)
  - "Problems of Discrimination and Extortion in the Building Trades:" Report, Koch Administration, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 49)
  - Promotional Material, 1922 (Box 15, Folder 50)
  - Promotional Material, 1942 (Box 15, Folder 51)
  - Promotional Material, 1981, 1986-1987 (Box 15, Folder 52)
  - Promotional Material, 1990, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 53)
  - Promotional Material, Undated (Box 15, Folder 54)
  - Public Relations Board, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 55)
  - Public Relations: Correspondence, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 56)
  - Public Relations: Correspondence, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 57)
  - Public Relations: Correspondence, 1987-1989 (Box 15, Folder 58)
  - Public Relations: Correspondence, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 59)
  - Publications, NYBC, 1941-2010 (Box 15, Folder 60)
  - Publicity, 1987-2007 (Box 15, Folder 61)
  - Real Estate Board of New York, 1984-1986 (Box 15, Folder 62)
  - Real Estate Board of New York: Don McGuirk's Talk to, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 63)
  - Real Estate Institute, New York University, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 64)
  - Real Estate Weekly, Issue Covering Trade Associations, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 65)
  - Rebuilding America Conference (I), 1994 (Box 15, Folder 66)